I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
（竜介(りゅうすけ)）来たぞ
（千葉(ちば)）どこどこ？ どこ？
-Over there!
-Where?! Where?!
何だよ…
What?
（千葉）男じゃん！
It's a guy!
Hey...When are you gonna
introduce me to your sister?
おい 一体 いつ
オネーチャン紹介してくれんだよ
こらぁっ！
（平(たいら)）お前ら… 仲がいいんだな
I see that you're good friends...
（竜介）いてっ
（千葉）だりゃーっ！
Ouch!
（千葉）いてえっ！
そいつ… ホントに歌えんのか？
Can he really sing?
さっ 早くスタジオ入って
セッション始めよーぜ！
Well, let's get to the studio
and start our session.
What? We're not going for drinks?
（千葉）
えーっ 飲みじゃないのかよ！
（竜介）お前なぁ…
Listen, you...
（千葉）
しゃーねぇ ガツンと歌いますか
Oh, well...I guess I'll
just have to belt it out.
（平）よろしく頼むぜ
I'm looking forward to it.
-Okay, okay. Well, let's go.
-Yeah...
（千葉）オーケー オーケー
じゃ 行こうぜ
"Hyodo and the Jaguar"
（真帆(まほ)）そろそろ 上がろっかな
I think I'll get out now.
Yeah...
（真帆）コユキも上がらない？
Won't you come out too, Koyuki?
Yeah...
（斎藤(さいとう)のいびき）
（真帆）コユキ
（コユキ）ん…
Koyuki...
You can have this.
（真帆）これ あげるよ
（コユキ）えっ？
あ… これって…
Why, this is...
（真帆）フフッ
ダイイング・ブリードの—
It's the pick that
Eddy of the Dying Breed used.
エディが使ったピックだよ
But...isn't that important to you?
それって—
大切な物じゃないのかな
（真帆）昔 ステージで拾ったんだ
I picked it up at a performance
long ago. It's my treasure.
私の宝物
I can't accept this.
もらえないよ
コユキ…
（コユキ）ん？
Koyuki...
Take good care of it!
大事にしろよーっ！
（コユキ）うわっ… うわぁっ！
Thanks!
ありがとう！
Yeah...
Sorry for calling you out so late at night.
（平）悪いな
こんな時間に呼び出して
Don't worry about it.
So, what did you want?
（栄二(えいじ)）なーに 気にしないで
で 用事って何？
I've been thinking about the band,
and I've reached a decision.
（平）バンドのこと
自分なりに考えて結論を出したんだ
And?
I've decided to join Ryusuke's band.
（平）竜介のバンドに
入ることに決めた
Taira-kun...Are you serious?!
平君… それ本気なのか？
I've always made decisions
based on my instincts.
俺は いつでも
自分の勘を信じて行動してきた
I've done everything I could...
（栄二）できる限りのことは
してきたつもりだ…
-It's magic...
-Magic?
（平）マジックなんだ
（栄二）マジック？
Ryusuke's band has the magic
I've been searching for.
竜介のバンドには—
俺がずっと探してた
マジックがありそうな気がする
See you around, Eiji.
じゃあな 栄二
Damn that Ryusuke!
（栄二）
ちくしょう… 竜介のヤツ
Damn him!
ちくしょう！
-Good morning.
Hey, Tanaka. I see some
sort of confidence in you lately.
（田辺(たなべ)）おい 田中
最近のお前見てると
何か顔に自信を感じるぞ
Oh...Really?
ん？ そうかな
Something must have happened.
Is it a girl?
何か あっただろ？ あ～ 女か？
A girl? No, but I have learned
how to do the butterfly kick.
女？ いや… バタフライは
泳げるようになったけどね
That girl wearing the No. 55 T-shirt
was so cute! A good singer, too!
55Ｔシャツ着てた子
かわいかったぞー 歌うまいしさぁ
-Oh, that's Maho-chan!
-Maho?
あ 真帆ちゃんだ
マ～ホ～？
Come on! Introduce me, will you?!
おお もう 俺にも紹介しろよ！
Nishimoto-sensei is out on maternity leave,
so here is her replacement.
（本堂）産休で休まれてる
西本(にしもと)先生に代わって—
きょうから このクラスの副担任を
やってもらう先生を紹介します
Uh...Ogasawara-sensei!
え～ 小笠原(おがさわら)先生！
Hello, everyone!
（桃子(ももこ)）
皆さん はじめまして！
Uh...I'm Momoko Ogasawara!
I'll be teaching music!
えっと 小笠原桃子といいます
担当は音楽です！
Since we're so close in age,
you can call me Momo-chan!
皆さんとは 年も近いし…
気楽に桃(もも)ちゃんって呼んでね！
-Awright!
-Momo-chan!
（男子生徒たち）は～い！
（男子生徒１・２）
桃ちゃーん
Man, that substitute is so hot!
（田辺）いやー 今度の副担任
かわいいよな～
"Just call me Momo-tan!"
“私のこと
桃ちゃんって呼んで！”って…
Hey, Tanaka, are you listening?!
おい 田中 聞いてんのかよ～？
Over there...
あそこ…
（田辺）ん？
Momo-chan!
桃ちゃ～んっ
Uhh, Sensei?
先生？
どわぁっ！
（コユキ）あ…
-I feel like giving up teaching.
-Huh?!
（桃子）私…
もう教師やめたくなっちゃった
After all, no one listens
to me during class...
（桃子）だって… 授業中—
誰も私の言うこと
ちゃんと聞いてくれないんだもん
お 俺 聞いてました！
すっげ～ 聞いてました！
I was listening! Really listening!
Right, Tanaka?!
なっ田中？
I hear you're good at singing, Tanaka-kun!
田中君って 歌がうまいんだってね
え… 何で？
-Where'd you hear that?
-I heard from Nishimoto-sensei.
西本先生から聞いたの
This guy can really sing!
The other day, he...
こいつ なかなか
歌うまいんですよ～ この間も…
I've been put in charge of the
choir contest for the Culture Festival.
私 文化祭の合唱コンクール
任されたんだ
That's great!
それは すごい！
I'd like you to lead
the class, Tanaka-kun!
田中君には クラスの陣頭指揮を
とってもらうわね！
-Eh? T-Tanaka-kun...
-Leading the class?
た 田中君が…
（コユキ）陣頭指揮？
I'm counting on you!
（桃子）よろしくね！
-Yes, ma'am!
（コユキ・田辺）オッス！
（桃子）ありがと！
Thank you!
"Music Room"
"Light Music Club"
-If I could have any wish granted now,
-I'd want wings
-Say, isn't the soccer game today?
-I'm supposed to shop with Mariko!
（男子生徒）なあ きょうってさ…
（女子生徒１）きょう マリコと…
I'm sorry. I have to go.
（女子生徒２）すいませーん
きょう用事あって
Come on! This is serious stuff!
（コユキ）
みんな… ちゃんとやろうよ
-Let's stop by Lotteria.
-Yeah!
（女子生徒３）ロッテリ寄ってこー
（女子生徒２）うん
Momoko-sensei made this printout
for us! Let's memorize the lyrics-
（コユキ）このプリント
桃子先生が作ってくれたんだよ
これで歌詞 覚えてさ…
（兵藤(ひょうどう)）
チッ… うるせえんだよ お前
You're annoying. If you wanna
do this, why not do it yourself?
やりたきゃ１人でやりゃいいだろ
あん？
Everyone...Let's practice harder tomorrow!
（桃子）みんな！
あしたは ちゃんと練習しようね！
-What a ditz!
-Who has time for this?
（女子生徒４）バッカじゃな～い？
（女子生徒５）やってらんないわよ
I'll be waiting for you!
先生 待ってるから！
（田辺）うん うん
I'll be waiting!
待ってるからね…
（田辺）うん
Man, that was scary.
（田辺）ビビったよ～
If Hyodo sets his sights on you,
you're in serious trouble.
おい 兵藤に目ぇつけられたら
マジ ヤベえぞ～
If you go up against him, you're dead!
ホント あいつに逆らったら
おしまいだからな
Hey! Koyuki!
（泉(いずみ)）お～い コユキ～！
Izumi-chan!
泉ちゃん！
Did you hear? Ryusuke-kun's
new band finally has a name!
知ってる？
竜介君の新しいバンドの名前
決まったんだよ！
His new band?
新しい… バンド？
Would you believe...it's Beck!
なんと… 「BECK(ベック)」だよ！
（コユキ）犬？
-His dog?
-Oh, that weird dog?
あ～ あの変な犬か！
Chiba-kun had the bright idea!
千葉君が思いつきで つけたんだ～
（コユキ）ハハハ…
He thought up all kinds of weird names
（泉）千葉君たら「青いイナズマ」
とか「はだしの悪魔」とか—
like Blue Lightning, Naked Devils,
and Dream Travelers.
「ドリームトラベラーズ」とか
変な名前ばっかり言ってたんだよ～
-Get real!
-It's true!
また～
（泉）え 本当だよ～
（田辺）また～
（泉）フフフ…
You want to join the Light Music Club?
軽音楽部 入りたいの？
ん～ やめたほうが
いいかもしれない
Maybe you shouldn't.
Why not? I thought I might make
some friends I can talk music with.
何で？
音楽のことが話せる友達が
できるかなって思ったんだけど…
But I haven't heard
anything good about that club.
でも あそこのいいウワサって
ホント聞いたことないぞ
I haven't heard a thing, either.
俺も全然 聞いたことない
ふ～ん…
"Music Room"
"Light Music Club"
"Cultural Festival"
"One Day Left"
Do you think we'll be ready
in time for the festival tomorrow?
（男子生徒１）これで
あしたの本番 間に合うかな～
Do you think we'll be ready
in time for the festival tomorrow?
We'll make sure we are.
（女子生徒１）間に合わせるの！
Think our coffee shop will make money?
（男子生徒２）
喫茶って もうかんのかな？
No, let's offer curry!
（女子生徒２）
やっぱ カレー出そうよー
To think that no one's
practicing for tomorrow...
（コユキ）誰も あしたに備えて
練習してないとは…
A Jaguar!
ジャガー…
And you know...
-Tanaka!
-Whattaya think you're doing?!
田中！
（取り巻き１）
こら！ 勝手に何やってんだ！
-I'm sorry!
-I'll slap you upside your head!
（コユキ）ごめんなさい！
（取り巻き２）シバくぞこんにゃろ
But...This is a Jaguar, right?
でも… これってジャガーでしょ
（兵藤）ん？
A Jaguar like the one
Kurt Cobain of Nirvana used.
ニルヴァーナのカート・コバーンが
持ってたジャガー
-I've always wanted to play-
-Try playing it.
１度 弾いてみたかったんだ
（兵藤）弾いてみろよ
（取り巻きたち）え？
（コユキ）いいの？
You're sure?
（兵藤）アハハハ…！
何だよ お前のギター
What's with your playing?!
（取り巻き２）っていうか
笑い止まんねー ハハハ…
Man, I can't stop laughing!
ハハハ… 腹いてー！
My sides hurt!
（取り巻き２）お前さぁ…
いつから弾いてんのよ？ ん？
Listen. How long've you been playing?
（コユキ）
いや… 一応 夏休みからだけど…
Well, uh...since summer break.
斎藤さんていう—
I'm learning from a man named Saito-san.
He loves British rock.
ブリティッシュロックが好きな人に
教わってるんだ
（取り巻き２）
誰だよ その斎藤って？
Who the heck is Saito?
そんな 訳分かんねえヤツに
教わってたら—
If you learn from a nobody like him
you'll always be the butt of jokes.
お前 いつまでたったって
笑いもんだぜ！ フフフッ…
俺のことは
いくら笑ったってかまわない！
You can laugh at me all you like!
けど 斎藤さんのことを
悪く言うのは やめてくれないか！
But could you stop insulting Saito-san?!
は～あ？
Huh?!
お前 ウザいんだよ！
You're a pain, you know? Damn you!
この！
（コユキ）うわっ あ！
（コユキ・取り巻き２）あっ
（取り巻きたち）あ～あ…
（兵藤）おい 田中～
Hey, Tanaka...Do you know
whose Jaguar that is?
お前 そのジャガーが…
誰のモンか知ってんのか？
今のは… 俺のせいじゃない
It wasn't my fault.
（取り巻き３）
おい！ 校舎裏で始まんぞ！
-He's about to start one behind the school!
-Start one?
始まる？
（兵藤）おい 田中！
Hey, Tanaka. I'll introduce
the owner of that Jaguar.
ジャガーの持ち主を 紹介するぜ
（米原(よねはら)）しょうがねーだろ
What can I do? I don't
have what I don't have.
ないもんは ねえんだ
（コユキ）あの人…
-That guy...
-It's Yonehara-sempai.
（兵藤）米原先輩だ
俺の小学校じゃ敵なしだった
No one could beat him
when he was in elementary school.
D-don't tell me that was his guitar?
ま まさか… あの人が持ち主？
Screw you!
ふざけるな！
おお… ぐっ… ぬお～…
（力也(りきや)）ナメんじゃねえ！
Don't take me for a fool!
That's Rikiya Kitazawa...
my childhood friend.
（兵藤）北沢力也… 俺の幼なじみ
Whoa...
すごい…
きょうのケンカ
ゲームの貸し借りが原因らしいぜ
That fight was over money
borrowed for video games.
-Huh?!
-Which means...
ええ…
（兵藤）てことは—
What do you think'll happen
if he finds out about his Jaguar?
ジャガーのこと力也君が知ったら…
どうなるかな？
Huh?
（力也）おい マサル！
んだよ 見てたのかよ
Hey, Masaru! You were watching?
（兵藤）
いやー たまたま通りかかってさ
No, we just happened by.
（力也）ふーん… そうか
Oh...Is that so?
（コユキ）ハァ…
“市内の14歳の中学生が—”
"A 14-year-old middle school student,
tired of being bullied at school,
“集団による イジメを苦に
中国ルートで三節棍(さんせつこん)を…”
used a tri-sectional staff from China and..."
ハァ…
I didn't tell Rikiya-kun about you, for now.
とりあえず力也君には—
お前のこと
ナイショにしといてやったよ
Koyuki!
（真帆）コユキー！
Oh...So it is you.
What's wrong? You look pale.
あー やっぱりコユキだ
どうかした？ 顔色悪いぞ
Yeah...But I'm fine now!
うん… でも もう大丈夫！
Aren't you sweating a lot?
（真帆）何か汗すごくない？
（コユキ）よいしょっ！
Ryusuke's in a recording studio right now.
（真帆）
今ね 竜介がスタジオ入ってるんだ
Oh, with Beck?
（コユキ）あー それ BECKでしょ？
Yeah...Won't you come watch with me?
（真帆）うん… でさ
一緒に見に行かない？
But...He never wanted to see me again...
でも… 俺 絶交されてるから…
ハハハ コユキ おなかすいてるの？
Koyuki, are you hungry?
I, uh, treated someone earlier,
so I'm broke...
さ さっき 人におごっちゃってさ
お金が… ないんだ
Want some fries?
ポテト食べる？
（コユキ）あ… サンキュー
Oh, uh...Thanks...
-Want a hamburger too?
-Yeah!
（真帆）ハンバーガーも食べる？
（コユキ）うん
Hurry up, will you?! Come on!
（真帆）早く来なよ！ おーい…
Koyuki!
コユキ！
I'll just take a peek from here.
俺… ここからのぞくだけで…
You serious?
（真帆）マジ？
-Oh, that bassist-!
-Yeah. Taira-kun joined up.
（コユキ）あっ あのベースの人？
（真帆）うん 平君が入ったんだ
Seems Ryusuke and Eiji
went head to head over it.
竜介のヤツ 栄二とは
かなり もめたみたいだけどね
He did?
（コユキ）あの人が…
Everyone looked all over for a drummer,
（真帆）ドラムはね みんなで
かなり探しまくったみたいだけど
but in the end they settled
on Togo-san of Serial Mama.
結局 シリアル・ママの東郷(とうごう)さんに
落ち着いたの
Oh...That guy?
あ あの人ね…
（東郷）ンフッ
They've been composing new songs,
（真帆）
今は オリジナル曲作って—
auditioning at live houses,
and sending out demo tapes.
ライブハウスの
オーディション受けたり—
デモテープを送ったりしてる
I've never seen Ryusuke so pumped up.
こんなに燃えてる竜介は
初めて見るよ
Koyuki? What's wrong?
コユキ？ どうした？
I'm sorry!
ごめん！
Koyuki?!
（真帆）コユキ！
ハァ… ハァ… ハァ…
I've gotta do something, too!
（コユキ）何か… 俺も！
Tanaka-kun?
（桃子）田中く～ん！
（コユキ）ん？
Momoko-sensei!
桃子先生！
It's finally time for the choir contest!
いよいよ合唱コンクール
本番だねっ！
I'm sorry I wasn't able to
live up to your expectations...
俺…
先生の期待に応えられなくて…
Nonsense...
ううん 田中君 ありがとね！
Tanaka-kun...Thank you.
Huh?
Let's sing with all our heart!
心を込めて 歌おうよ！
あっ 先生… オッス！
（桃子）フフッ
Sensei...
Right!
The 8th graders will sing "Give me Wings."
（アナウンス）２年４組の
合唱曲は「翼をください」です
-If I could have any wish granted now,
-I'd want wings
Man...I didn't think we'd be that bad.
いやー あそこまでひどいとはなぁ
We came in last...
and Momoko-sensei cried...
最下位だもんね
桃子先生 泣いてたし
あ… ギターの音？
（田辺）ふわぁ～あ…
Is that a guitar?
What is this?!
何だこりゃ…
They're having a wild time!
めちゃ盛り上がってんぞ！
Oh! Look at all those girls!
おおっ 女の子がいっぱいだ！
That guitar...
（コユキ）あのギター…
あ！ 兵藤！
（田辺）ホントだ
-It's Hyodo!
-You're right!
Next year, let's do a concert...
来年 ライブ出よう
Hyodo-kun...He's really good!
兵藤君…
すごいね
（コユキ）ジャーン！
イェイ！
Hey...Tanaka.
（兵藤）おーい 田中
あ… 兵藤君！
Hyodo-kun!
Your live performance was great!
ライブ 最高だったよ！
I was practicing an imaginary guitar!
俺 今 ギターの
イメージトレーニングをしてたんだ
Go and buy me a cola, soy milk,
a melon roll, and a curry bun.
コーラと豆乳と
メロンパンとカレーまん—
買ってこい
Your encore was so exciting!
Even Kazuko-sensei was dancing!
アンコールが
すごい盛り上がりだったよね！
和子(かずこ)先生まで踊りだしてさ
Bring them to the music room ASAP.
音楽室まで至急頼む
（コユキ）ぐ…
I ran into Rikiya-kun earlier.
（兵藤）
さっき力也君に会ったんだけどさ
He was steaming
about the scratch on the Jaguar.
あいつジャガーの傷のことで
めちゃくちゃ怒ってたぜ
He's searching all over
for the one who did it.
血眼で犯人捜してるよ
T-that last song was
a cover of Springs, right?!
さ… 最後の曲って
スプリングスのカバーだよね？
Listen! I don't wanna talk music with you!
（兵藤）あのさぁ！
お前と音楽の話 したくねーんだよ
If you don't want me to tell
Rikiya-kun about the scratch,
力也君に傷のこと
バラされたくないなら—
you'd better hurry up and do as I say!
さっさと俺の言うことを聞け！
Screw that...He can't order me around.
（コユキ）ふざけんな！
あんなヤツの言いなりになんか…
Hey! Rikiya-sempai's started a fight!
（男子生徒１）お～い！
力也先輩がケンカ始めたぞ～！
（柔道部員）ぐわぁっ！
Hey, isn't that the Judo Club captain?!
（男子生徒２）
おい 相手は柔道部の主将だろ？
うぉーっ だあっ！
I'm in a bad mood today!
きょうは機嫌がワリィんだよ
Don't complain just because
I skipped the room-cleaning!
掃除サボったくらいで
ガタガタ言うな！
あ コユキ！
Koyuki!
Melon roll, curry bun, cola, soy milk!
（コユキ）メロンパン カレーまん
コーラ 豆乳…
Melon roll, curry bun, cola, soy milk!
メロンパン カレーまん
コーラ 豆乳…
Melon roll, curry bun, cola, soy milk!
Melon roll? Weird...
メロンパン？
変なの… フンッ
"Fishing Hole"
This is bad! This goes
beyond being just a prank!
（東郷）ひどいな
いたずらにしちゃ度が過ぎてる
Let's report it to the police!
警察に届けよう！
I know who did it.
（竜介）犯人は分かってる
Eiji?
（平）栄二か？
Yeah...
The day the Les Paul was stolen,
I saw his car, too.
（千葉）レスポールが盗まれた日
あいつの車 俺も見たぜ！
Damn! Shall we go and pulverize his Strat?!
ちくしょう！ あいつのストラト
ぶっ壊し行くか！
Lucille.
ルシールだ
-Huh?
Lucille's the only one left.
（竜介）ルシールしかない
Lucille?
ルシール…
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Maybe I'll take a trip to where
the dropped pencil points.
（千葉）鉛筆が転んだ先に
旅に出ようかな
"Next Episode"
"Lucille"
Maybe I'll take a trip to where
the dropped pencil points.
"Next Episode"
"Lucille"
There's sure to be a dream lying there!
そこに
夢が落ちているから！